<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Webri.ng Changelog</title>
		<description>
			This RSS feed is to keep you updated with important changes to the Webri.ng platform. 
			Any significant updates will be posted here.
		</description>
		<link>https://webri.ng</link>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<webMaster>admin@webri.ng</webMaster>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:24:30 +1000</lastBuildDate>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:24:30 +1000</pubDate>

		<item>
			<title>Webri.ng Site Improvements</title>
			<link>https://webri.ng</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:24:30 +1000</pubDate>
			<description>
				We've recently published a few small improvements to the Webri.ng platform.
				The 'Example Markup' generation has been greatly improved. It no longer uses a HTML table element to layout the navigation elements.
				A bug related to site URLs that feature a named anchor has also been fixed. If you experience any difficulties with navigating a webring from a site with a named anchor, please update your navigation links to pass a properly encoded URL. Using the 'Get Example Markup' button will generate this for you.
				As always, if you experience any issues with the system please contact us at admin@webri.ng
			</description>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Webri.ng Site Index Parameter Updated</title>
			<link>https://webri.ng</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 19:22:47 +1000</pubDate>
			<description>
				A very observant Webri.ng user highlighted an issue that can occur when a site is removed from a webring.
				If a site is removed from a webring, 
				this can cause the 'previous' link for the next site in the ring to point to itself.
				To resolve this issue, 
				we've changed the URL parameter used to identify a site's current position in a webring from its numerical 'index' in the ring, 
				to passing the current site's URL in the 'via' parameter.
				This new solution is fully backwards-compatible with the existing system.
				The old 'index' parameter can still be used by current sites.
				The 'random' functionality has also been improved so that if the site index is passed
				the 'random' site function will not select the current site again.
				If you experience any issues with the new system please contact us at admin@webri.ng
			</description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
